[Superman] Something happened
during the fight.
My powers.
I can't be Superman
for you anymore.
[Jimmy] Clark. Clark.
Hey. Clark.
You okay. man?
Yeah. Yeah.
-Smile.
-[camera shutter clicks]
-Let's get one with you.
-I'm good. Jimmy.
You two are the ones nominated
for an award tonight.
You are nominated too.
Technically.
Superman was nominated.
But it's fine. I'm fine.
[musical horn honking]
[Steve] Good evening.
award co-nominees.
plus Clark.
Which one of you lucky kids
gets to ride up front with me?
[all] Uh...
[chuckles] Just kidding.
The back seat's
for nominees only.
Come on. Kent.
Make yourselves comfortable.
VIPs.
Back there. you've got
all weather floor mats.
adjustable protein shake sleeves
and check this. It's a curtain.
It's like Kent
and I aren't even here.
So you think Superman's
gonna show up tonight?
I'm... I mean. I'm sure
he'll try his best to make it.
I mean. he definitely
wants to be here.
He probably misses the city
as much as it misses him.
Probably.
[Jimmy sighs] Poor Clark.
How long does it usually take
to open up
after your identity's
been shattered?
I'll see if we can talk tonight.
Speaking of tonight.
who's Kara bringing to the gala?
-Oh. you mean like a date?
-Yeah. a date.
She's the most eligible
bachelorette in Metropolis.
I don't think
she's bringing anyone.
She's been full time Supergirl
for the last month and...
Wait! Are you bringing a date?
Well. W.O.R.M.S..
W.O.R.M.S.. W.O.R.M.S..
-reached out to me again.
-Jimmy!
And as a man of business.
I have a contractual obligation
to go on one more date.
uh. tonight.
You're bringing a date to a gala
where Kara is receiving
an award?
Come on. You've seen Kara
on the apps.
She's moved on.
I can't wait until your date
turns you into an octopus
or a human skyscraper or...
Listen. I have this
all under control.
Nothing is gonna happen tonight.
[classical music playing]
You see. Lois.
this is a perfectly normal gala
with perfectly normal...
-[screams]
-[yelps]
The Daily Planet Interns
are being featured tonight.
So Mr. White says
we're your problem now.
What?
-[sighs]
-It's okay. Jimmy. I got this.
-But. Clark...
-It's all right.
It's really okay.
[whispering]
I need something to do.
Wait. I'm gonna go find...
[gala attendees gasping]
[gala attendee whispering]
She's here.
[applauding. cheering]
Kara.
[giggles] She's moved on.
I don't see a date.
Uh...
Hey. Kara!
Over here!
Lois Lane! Jimmy Flamebird!
[vehicle approaching.
tires squealing]
[camera shutter clicking]
Oh. Monsieur Olsen.
Bonsoir. cheri.
[kisses]
Wow! [chuckles] Hello.
You must be
Princess Marina Maru.
Maru. And please. James.
call me Marina.
Cat Grant. Daily Planet.
Is James Olsen
your date tonight?
Oh. oui. bien sur!
Jimmy brought a date.
Jimmy brought a date!
[opening music playing]
That's Jimmy's W.O.R.M.S. date.
Well. Jimmy's always had
a boyish charm.
-[Jimmy chuckling]
-[Lois] Boyish charm.
Anyway. I hope we get a chance
to talk tonight. Clark.
[Flip] The dress is fire.
-[flames billowing]
-[gala attendee screaming]
Uh. sorry. Lois. but I gotta go
get those rascals.
-Come here. you. Come on.
-[cat screeching]
-Lane.
-Vicki.
I can't believe
you turned down a job with me
to stay with
your deadweight boyfriend.
So much promise wasted.
I don't need to work for you
to be a great reporter. Vicki.
And by the way. we're nominated
in the same category.
So I think I'm doing just fine.
You mean co-nominated
with the Olsen kid?
You can't even win an award
without one of your
little boy toys at your side.
[scoffs]
Let's find out what
you're made of. shall we. Lane?
Whoever walks away with
the biggest scoop tonight wins.
Oh. you're on.
You talk a big game. Vicki.
but everyone knows
all that really counts
is what you can do.
[exclaims] Vicki Vale!
Can you believe I used to be
obsessed with her?
Hey. is everything okay?
Oh. yeah. Great.
Everything's great.
[Bizarro] I can help you.
[laughs]
[news anchor] Metropolis has
been missing its hero
for over a month now.
Supergirl is expected to be at
the humanitarian gala tonight
to accept her award.
But will Superman
be there to join her?
Mmm. my friend.
[classical music playing]
Jimmy.
introduce me to your date.
Who you brought to the gala
where I am receiving an award.
[chuckles] Kara. I. uh...
Ah. Supergirl.
You and Superman are greatly
admired even in Markovia.
Metropolis is fortunate
to have you as its guardian.
Thank you. Princess.
But it is Superman
who deserves all the credit.
You deserve the credit.
You saved the city.
And I I know the city's
confusing
and doesn't always know
how it feels.
But everybody in the city
really. really cares
about you. Kara and...
Ah. James Olsen.
You are so kind
to your platonic friend.
[Jimmy] Uh. I mean. I'm...
I'm just. uh...
Good evening and welcome
to Metropolis's 10th Annual
Humanitarian Gala.
[laughing. cheering]
My name is Silver St. Cloud.
And it is my honor
to be your host tonight.
Thank you for joining us here
at the Natural History Museum.
We have an impressive roster
of speakers
and so much charitable service
to recognize tonight.
So please find your seat.
Thank you.
[tense music playing]
Fox to vulture.
Entryway has been secured.
[Clark clears throat]
Uh. Kara. can you believe these
are the bones of a blue whale.
Earth's largest living animal?
Flip. Why don't you tell...
Uh-oh. Flip?
Hey. Clark.
won't you miss Kara's...
Don't worry. I'll be back
before Kara's award.
I promise.
Flip!
[Silver] It's my great
privilege to recognize not one.
but two courageous individuals
who put their lives
on the line for Metropolis
again and again.
Please. a huge round of applause
for Metropolis humanitarians.
-Superman and Supergirl.
-[applauding]
Thank you all.
Kal-El... Superman wishes
he could be here tonight.
but in his absence.
I humbly accept this award
for us both.
I can see why Superman
loves your Earth.
Although I am still new
to this planet.
it is already full
of people I love.
And friends I can count on.
Fox to Vulture. Exits are
locked and alarms are disabled.
Local feed redirected.
Ready to broadcast at your word.
-Princess Maru.
-Vicki. what are you...
You're so outspoken
in your beliefs.
Do you fear public backlash
or even persecution
for your endorsement
of free expression?
[Marina] I have received
several threats. yes.
But I always take
the necessary precautions.
I refuse to be silenced.
Hmm.
Leaving already. Lane?
[whining]
That's what you sound like.
[all laughing]
[grunts]
What's all this?
-[guard groans]
-[gasps]
Who's there?
[gasps]
Uh. I think we need to tell
someone about this.
Like who?
Flip?
Kids?
[groans] Anyone?
Be really great to have
super-hearing right about now.
[disembodied voices
whispering indistinctly]
Flip?
Um. stop being creepy.
What in the...
[disembodied voices
whispering indistinctly]
speaking indistinctly]
[Flip screaming]
Flip!
[Lois] So you have absolutely
no opinions
on the growing armed
presence here tonight?
Do you have thoughts
on anything?
Fine. Who's in charge here?
[Silver] That would be me.
Oh. hi. Silver. [chuckles]
I... I just wanted to...
Have you seen...
I'm a big fan
of your work. Lois.
You're a terrific reporter.
Oh. wow. Thank you.
But these interrogations are
kind of bringing down the vibe.
You know what I mean?
The added security is
Princess Maru's private detail.
That's all.
I'm sorry. Silver.
I'm just in this
stupid competition
with Vicki tonight and...
Tonight's awards
aren't enough for you two?
Okay. I guess I'm always in
a stupid competition with Vicky.
but. I mean. what's enough?
I don't know.
But I do know
that if you need an award
to tell you that you're enough.
-you'll never get there.
-[groans]
Just do your best.
And if you can celebrate
whatever that brings you
with the people you love.
well. that's as much
as anybody gets.
Wait. Where are
the people I love?
[dramatic music playing]
Get away from them!
My powers.
Is everyone all right?
Anybody hurt?
You're hurt. Clark.
Where's Superman?
I... I'm sorry. I...
[door opens]
-Come on. We have to go now.
-[soldier] Hey. you!
Clark?
Anyone?
This is Vulture.
I got another stray.
[screams]
-Shh.
-Clark. there's a man.
Yeah. His friend just shot me.
[gasps]
[grunts]
[grunts] Vulture to Fox.
I have strays in the hallway.
I'll take care of them.
Confirm when you have hands
on the princess.
Hands on the princess?
And now please join me
in welcoming
our esteemed keynote speaker.
Her Royal Highness.
Princess Marina Maru
of Markovia.
[applauding. cheering]
Kara.
Jimmy. Princess Maru
has a problem.
Armed men have broken in
and they're after her.
I am Princess Marina Maru.
But you may call me...
Dr. Poison!
[crowd gasping]
[Dr. Poison] I am here to
reverse the Anthropocene era.
curing our Mother Earth
of the disease of humankind!
-[Lois] Jimmy!
-I guess I have a type.
And what better place
to start this revolution
than here at the mausoleum
you've created
for the animals of Le Monde.
Prepare to leave on four legs
or not at all!
[roars]
[screams]
-[crowd screaming]
-[animals screeching]
You! Stop!
Ah. Supergirl.
Such a pity my poison
does not work on you.
but you have other problems. no?
At this very moment.
my henchmen are
at the Metropolis Dam.
Ready to release my poison
directly into the city's
water supply.
Can you be
in two places at once?
Kara. go save the city.
Dr. Poison is
my contractual obligation.
[grunts]
[soldier grunting]
Open up!
Uh. how are you gonna stop him?
I...
[Lois] Wait.
[grunts]
[gas hissing]
[coughing]
[screeching]
Any ideas on how to stop
Dr. Poison?
-Uh...
-She's your date.
Wait. Your boyish charm.
Use your boyish charm!
I... I don't think
it works like that.
Oh. no. No. no. no.
I don't want to be a wolf again.
Uh. what?
This way. kids.
We're almost there.
[growling]
It's over!
The guard.
I thought his name was Vulture.
Back up. kids! Back up!
[roars]
[Dr. Poison] Get to the chopper!
[Jimmy] Wait!
Princess Maru!
James?
Princess. please listen to me.
[Dr. Poison]
This form suits you. James.
But sadly. this must be adieu.
But didn't you feel
our connection?
Our animal attraction?
I... Well...
[dramatic music playing]
[crocodile hissing]
Everyone. keep going.
Lois. what are you...
Lois?
[grunts]
Lois!
[screams]
[cat meows]
Are you...
Up here. Smallville.
Cat?
Yeah. yeah. yeah. Keep going.
James. you beautiful fool.
You were just a pawn
in my world-altering game.
A handsome pawn. oui.
but a pawn seulement.
I'm sorry. What was that?
I can't understand you
because of your gas mask.
Do not think me cruel. James.
But I only arranged
a date with you
to gain access to this event.
But now I must shed you
like so much snakeskin.
But wait.
Just one more thing.
[roars]
[screams]
[bones cracking]
That's enough!
[coughing]
Shark to Fox.
Operation Make a Splash
has been compromised.
Allons-y. Maintenant!
Bad dog.
[gunfire]
[explosion]
[barks]
Huh? Who...
[animals screeching]
James. I am so sorry to have
broken your fragile heart.
Don't worry. you didn't.
There are more sharks
in the sea.
my delicious pound cake.
You will forget
our restless rendezvous
and someday find true love.
I'm already in love
with someone.
I've just been really.
really stupid about it.
Of course. c'est moi.
Her name is Kara.
[scoffs] Whatever makes
you feel better. James.
Au revoir!
[sighs]
[meows]
[gasps] Silver. Hi.
Lois. I wanted
to congratulate you
on your award.
[gasps] I won? [gasps]
I mean. thanks. Silver.
[chuckles] Enjoy the rest
of your night. Miss Lane.
Well. obviously. the work
itself is its own reward.
Here. Flip. Do you want this?
-Uh. thanks.
-[Vicki groans]
Okay. she's gone. Give it back.
Ooh! It's so shiny!
-Jimmy Flamebird!
-[Jimmy screams]
Why did you share feelings
with Dr. Poison
that you would not
share with me?
I thought it seemed
like you moved on.
You were on the apps.
You... You'd been dating people?
No. I wanted to be together.
You ran away and and played
your stupid Earth games.
Then Kal-El became distant.
And... And you stopped
talking to me.
I... I thought you just
wanted to be friends.
How can you be my friend
if you hide
when I need you most?
I'm sorry. Kara.
I didn't understand
how you felt.
You did not ask.
Clark. we did it!
We saved the city.
Jimmy and I won the award.
-And you...
-I didn't do anything. Lois.
You saved the kids.
Jimmy defeated Dr. Poison.
Kara saved the city.
All I did was get shot
and locked in a closet.
Metropolis needed a hero.
and all I could give them
was Clark Kent.
Hey. I love Clark Kent.
Well. he's no Superman.
Clark. you can't spend
the rest of your life
comparing yourself to someone
you might never be again.
And what am I supposed to do?
Who am I supposed to be?
[screams]
Huh?
[both scream]
[theme music playing]